tazamart.pk 2017-04-14

# Privacy Policy - TazaMart

We at  ** _TazaMart_ **(hereinafter also referred to as “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, “ **our** ”) understand our users and customers (hereinafter also referred to as “ **you** ”, “ **your** ”) concern and care about regarding collection, usage, sharing and disclosure of personal information. We take your privacy seriously.

This Privacy Policy (hereinafter also referred to as “ **Policy** ”) outlines the manner in which _TazaMart_ may collect, use and disclose your personal data, whether through the _TazaMart_ website at  _[http://www. _TazaMart_.com](http://www.tazamart.com/)_ (“ **Site** ”), the _TazaMart_ software or mobile application (“ **App** ”), or otherwise in the course of our normal business operations.

 **Consent**

By accessing the Site, App and/or providing personal data to _TazaMart_ , you hereby acknowledge that you have read this Policy and give your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal data by _TazaMart_ in accordance with this Policy.

If you do not consent to the terms of this Policy, please do not access the Site, App or provide your personal data to _TazaMart_. Moreover, if you are under 18 years of age, please do not use the Site or App, or attempt to register an Account or send any personal data about yourself to us. We at _TazaMart_ do not knowingly collect or solicit personal data from those below the age of 18.

 _TazaMart_ reserves the right to amend the prevailing Privacy Policy at any time and will place any such amendments on this Site or App. Your continuous use of the Site, App, and the services offered by _TazaMart_ implies consent to any changes made.

 **Data Collection – Personal & Non-Personal Information**

 _To fulfill your order, we need your personal information._

Your personal information that we may collect depends on your usage and includes, but is not limited to, when users visit our Site, use our app, fill out a form, communicate to use via email, phone or any other channel or platform, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on _TazaMart_.

Users may be asked for, based upon relevance, name, gender, email address, residential address, contact number and other details. You may, however, visit _TazaMart_ anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us.

You may also refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website related activities.

 _Non-Personal Information:_ Along with your personal information, _TazaMart_ collects data that is sent automatically by your web browser, computer, mobile or tablet device.  This may or may not include your IP address, the address of the specific web page or pages you visited, information about the device you are using, date and time of your visit, and other information.  Please check the settings of your browser and/or device if you want to know what data is automatically sent or if you wish to change your settings.  Kindly peruse the section on “Cookies” below for more information on automatically collection information.

If you wish to access, amend, or update your personal details, you may do so at any time by accessing your Account settings through the Site or App.  You may also contact us at contact@ _TazaMart_.pk.  You are responsible for providing us with correct and updated information and ensuring the security of your password at all times.

 **Data Usage**

Data collection rests on the premise that it allows us to fulfill your order and improve our products and services, personalize it based upon your needs and preferences and enhance user experience (UX).

We do not sell, rent or share your personal data with any third party. The only time that your data may be disclosed to a third party would be:

  * To help our partner, affiliate or subsidiary in order fulfillment
  * To credit card and payment processing companies
  * For order fulfillment to our technology, marketing & logistics service providers
  * To agents, subcontractors and service providers acting on behalf of _TazaMart_
  * In compliance with the law, statute, regulation, government order, etc.

We may also, from time to time, collaborate with our partners, affiliates, and third-parties for joint marketing and promotional activities including, but not limited to, campaigns, contents, special deals, etc. We may be required to share your information in such collaborations.

 **Data Security**

Data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures are in place to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of _your_ personal information, username, password, transaction information and data entered on _TazaMart._

 **Links to Other Sites  **

 _TazaMart_ may provide links to other sites that may be of relevance and interest to you.  We have no control over, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Linked Sites, and you hereby waive any claim against us with respect to the Linked Sites.

 **Cookies   **

 _Cookies_ are miniature text files that help _our_ server to recognize _your_ computer as a unique visitor whenever _you_ visit certain pages on _TazaMart_. _Your_ Internet Protocol (IP) Address saves time and unnecessary clicks and helps _us_ improve User Experience (UX).

Cookies are never used to obtain information about any user, such as for targeted advertising purposes. _You_ can set _your_ browser settings and not accept any cookies; but that would restrict _TazaMart_ ’s effectiveness. _We_ assure our customers that none of our cookies contain any private or personal details and are virus free.

To find more information regarding cookies _you_ can visit https://www.allaboutcookies.org or also inquire on how to remove cookies from a browser at https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html.

 _Our_ _website_ uses Google Analytics, which is a Google. Inc provided service (“Google”). Google analytics places text files (cookies) on _user’s_ computer to help track and analyze the _website_ as to how it is being used by different _users_. All information generated by these cookies is transferred and stored on the servers of Google in USA. Google uses all gathered information to evaluate how the _website_ is used and compiles the information in form of reports which is then made available to _website_ operators in form of activity on their sites along with offering other services also related to activity on the _website_ and use of internet. Google may also pass out the information received to other third parties whenever the law requires it to do so or wherever any third party is used by Google to process the information on their behalf. Google does not associate IP addresses with any other Google held date. _Website users_ can at any time refuse cookies use via selecting suitable settings in their browsers. Ho _we_ ver doing so will restrict users from enjoying the full functionality of _TazaMart_. Through using this site, visitors offer consent to Google’s processing of _your_ data in the manner and for the purpose defined above.

 **Indemnity**

Your usage of _TazaMart_ implies that _you_ are solely responsible for ensuring the security of _your_ personal information, such as username and password, and indemnify TazaMart of all responsibility for any misuse of the abovementioned unless when it is due to TazaMart’s mistake or oversight.
